好  该结婚了
Okay, this is it.
你确定要这么做
You sure you wanna do this?
你好  罗斯太太
Hello, Mrs. Ross. Woo-hoo!
你好  瑞秋先生
Well, hello, Mr. Rachel.
哇哦  我的天哪
Whoa! Oh, my God.
菲比  快点  快  快  快
Come on, Pheebs, hurry! Hurry, hurry, hurry.
好啦  好啦
Okay! Okay!
我的天哪  大家都要结婚吗
Oh, my God! Is everybody getting married?
教堂里不准奔跑
Agh. No running in the chapel.
你少跟我来这  嘿
Hey, don't you give me any of your... Hey!
嗨  嘿
Hi. Hey!
你们来干什么
What are you doing here?
罗斯和瑞秋留言  说要结婚
Ross and Rachel left us a message saying they were getting married!
你们不是来找他们的吗  当然是
Isn't that why you guys are here? Yes.
不然我们来这儿干什么啊
Why else would we be here? Ha-ha-ha.
怎么样  我们来晚了吗
Well, what happened? Did we miss it?
我们也没赶上
We actually missed it.
可能都是因为教堂里不能奔跑
Well, Maybe you wouldn't have if you could run in the chapel!
真是太扯了
This is insane.
有什么关系呢  又不是真结婚
What's the big deal? It's not like it's a real marriage.
什么
What?
在赌城结婚  只在赌城内有效
If you marry in Vegas, you're only married in Vegas.
你在说什么  在赌城结婚到处都有效
What are you talking about? If you get married in Vegas you’re married everywhere.
真的
Really?
是啊
Yeah.
我的妈呀
Oh, my God.
啊  随便啦
Oh, well.
老友记  第六季  第1集  离开拉斯维加斯
Friends  S06E01  The One After Vegas
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
我们为什么躺在一起
Why are we in bed together?
我不知道
I don't know.
你有穿衣服吗
Do you have any clothes on?
有
Yes.
真的  没有
Really? No.
但是我们没有
But we didn't have...
嘿咻吧
...sex, did we?
我不太记得昨晚的事
I don't remember much about last night.
一切都好模糊
It was such a blur. Ha, ha. Oh.
我记得我有笑   我一直笑
I remember laughing. I laughed a lot. Uh-huh?
而且我们没怎样
Then we didn't have sex.
我们真的醉得很惨
Oh, I mean, we were really drunk.
幸好没干什么蠢事
I'm glad we didn't do anything stupid.
可不是吗
Tell me about it.
（新婚大囍）
菲比  早
Morning, Pheebs. Mm.
我的电影取消拍摄了
Well, my movie has been officially canceled.
哇啊  乔伊  好可惜喔  你要不要吃我的早餐
Mm. Joey, I'm so sorry. You want some of my breakfast?
算了  我沮丧的吃不下啊
Nah, I’m too depressed to eat.
过五分钟再说吧
I'll probably eat in, like, five minutes.
我只好跟你们回去了  飞机是几点
So I guess I'll fly home with you. What time is your flight?
我的计程车呢  我用不着了
What about my cab? I don't need that anymore.
乔伊  你跟我借车  就要开回去
No, Joey! you borrowed my cab. You have to drive it back.
我不想自己开回去  太寂寞了
I don't wanna drive back by myself. I get lonely.
干脆你来陪我
Oh, ooh. How about if you come with me?
我不知道   要开很久  一定很好玩
I don't know, it's a long trip. That would be great.
我们可以聊天玩游戏
We could talk and play games.
这是让友谊变新鲜的好机会
This could be our chance to, like, renew our friendship.
你要我跟你〝友谊复兴〞
Are you asking me to have a "frienaissance"?
是吧
Sure?
好吧   虽然没这个必要  但我一直爱着你
Heh. All right, although I don't think we need one. I never stopped loving you.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
有谁跟盖勒博士夫妇讲过话啊
So, has anyone talked to Dr. and Mrs. Geller yet?
他们有留言给我   应该快到了
Mm-hm. They left me a message. They'll be here.
服务生呢  我饿死了
Where is the waitress? I'm starving.
这是自助餐
It's a buffet, man.
我可以捞本了
Here's where I win all my money back!
我有事找你
I gotta talk to you.
好
Sure.
什么事
What's up?
摩妮卡和我昨晚差点结婚
Monica and I almost got married last night.
天哪
My God!
这可是大事
That's huge! Ha-ha-ha, hey.
等等  为什么没找我去
Wait a minute. Why wasn't I invited?
谁要当你的伴郎  不要说罗斯  不准说罗斯
And who was gonna be your best man? Don't say Ross. Do not say Ross.
我觉得我们还没准备好  我很爱她
I just don't think that Monica and I are ready to get married yet! Y’know? I mean, I love her...
但看到罗斯他们从教堂冒出来
...but seeing Ross and Rachel come out of that chapel...
我突然惊觉  我们进展得太快了
...was like a wake-up call that Monica and I are moving so fast, you know.
我要怎么讲才不会让她心碎
How do I tell her without crushing her?
就说她不是结婚的料
Tell her she's not marriage material.
什么
What?
女生都这么对我说
Girls say it to me all the time.
相信我   要是她和我一样  一定会如释重负
And believe me, And if she's anything like me, she's just gonna be relieved.
我该怎么说  这样太快了
How do I tell Chandler that it's too soon?
他一定会心碎  觉得我不爱他了
It’s gonna break his heart, he’s not gonna think that I don’t love him anymore.
你是不爱他了  我爱
Well, you don't. Yes, I do.
很好  我只是在测试你
Good. I was just testing you.
嘿  噢  嗨
Hey. Oh, hi.
我们刚才聊到培根
Y’know, We were just talking about bacon.
不对  我们是在聊网球
No, we were talking about tennis.
网球比较像真的
Tennis is more believable.
嘿  嘿
Hey.
嗨  谢谢
Hi. Thank you.
咖啡
Coffee. Heh. Mm.
怎样  你们要谈谈
What? Are we gonna talk...
昨晚的事吗
...about what you guys did last night, or?
昨晚什么事  昨晚又没怎样
What do you mean "last night"? Nothing, uh, happened last night.
罗斯把大家都找去看了
Uh-huh. Ross invited us all to watch.
瑞秋  我们不可能错过朋友的婚礼
Rach, we weren't gonna miss our friends marrying.
谁结婚了
Huh, who got married?
你们啊
You did?
什么
What? Heh.
我们哪有结婚  怎么可能  别闹了
Wh...? Hello. We didn't get married. No, we didn't. That’s ridiculous!...
等等  我们  我记得去过教堂
Wait, wait, wait. I remember being in a chapel.
我们醉成那样  不可能被批准结婚的
They would not let us get married when we were that drunk.
醉成那样  也当然可能
They let you get married when you’re drunk!
在赌城结婚的人通常都醉了
Most people who marry in Vegas are drunk.
我现在就醉了
Heh, I'm drunk right now.
早餐不能喝鸡尾酒啊  我在度假
I can't have a mimosa with breakfast? I'm on vacation.
你们要怎么办
What are you gonna do?
看来得找个离婚律师了
Well, I guess we find a divorce lawyer. Uh-huh.
我想罗斯已经有一个了
Well, I think, I think Ross already has one.
这次会免费吧
Now, this one's free, right?
你办了两次  所以会送一次
Because you paid for the first two, third one free.
你笑吧  丢脸的是你
Laugh it up, but the joke's on you...
我们不必离婚
...because we don't need to get divorced.
只要办理注销  住校
We're just gonna get an annulment. an annulment?
罗斯  学校可帮不了你
Ross, I don't think surgery is the answer here.
那是你的正字标记
Oh, that's your thing!
什么
What?
你的正字标记  你是专门离婚的人
Your thing, Y’know? that you're the guy who gets divorced.
没错
Oh, yeah.
那才不是我的正字标记
No, no, that's not "my thing."
我并不爱离婚
I do not love getting divorced.
你当然爱  这是你第三次离婚
Yes, you do. This is your third divorce.
你爱离婚爱到搞不好会娶它
You love divorce so much, you're probably gonna marry it...
然后婚姻破裂  你又得离婚  离婚名人
...and then it won't work out, so you're gonna have to divorce it, divorcing guy.
我醉得好厉害
I'm so drunk.
你觉得我们该怎么办  我不知道
So, what should we do? I don't know.
但我知道我爱你
I know I love you.
我也知道我爱你
I know I love you. Heh.
那我们还要
So where are we on the whole "going back...
回过头去结婚吗  我爱你
...to where they have the marriages" thing? I love you.
问得好
That's a good question.
昨晚我们让骰子决定
Look umm, Last night we let the dice decide.
也许应该再让命运决定一次  我爱你
Maybe we should leave it up to fate again. I love you!
没错   有征兆我们才结婚
Yes, We don't get married unless there's a sign.
好吗  那么
Okay? So say, uh...
要是你又掷出8来  就表示我们绝对应该结婚
You roll another eight, then there’s a definite sign that we should get married.
好  8就结婚
All right. Eight we get married...
其他就不结
...but 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10, 11, 12, we don't get married.
听起来不错  好
Sounds great. Okay.
有人要掷了
Hey, we got a shooter.
请押注
Money, please.
好了吗  好了
Ready? Ready.
来个8吧
Come on, eight.
没错  8
Yes, yes, eight.
8   3加5是8
Eight, easy eight.
哇   居然真的是8  真是太不可能了
Wow, I can't believe I rolled an eight. That was so unlikely.
那就结婚吧  我猜
Well, let's get married. I guess. Aah.
等等   那不是双四八  我昨晚掷的是双四八
Wait a minute. That wasn't hard eight!  Last night I rolled a hard eight.
没错  这个8不对  不能结婚了  妈的
That’s right! It was the wrong kind of eight. No wedding! Damn it!
我好想结婚喔
Agh! Aah! Unh, I wanted it so bad!
收拾行李去  好
Wanna go pack? Yeah.
我们没做错吧  当然  没错
We're doing the right thing, right? Oh, of course we are.
我们让命运决定
Heh, we left it up to fate.
如果我们应该结婚  一定会有明确的征兆
If we were supposed to get married, there would be a clear-cut sign.
好  你还剩十九个问题  要好好把握
Okay, you have 19 questions left. Use them wisely.
快点  乔伊  你不能赢了  如果你不问
Come on, Joey. You can't win if you don't ask any...
问题
questions!
怎样啦  你说会很好玩
What? You promised me a fun road trip.
结果我们开了六小时  你就睡了五个小时半
We've been on the road for 6 hours, and you've been asleep for 5 and a half.
到下一个休息站就换手  你给我一路开回去
We are switching at the next rest stop and you are going to drive all the way back!
这是对你的惩罚   贪睡鬼
That will be your punishment, you greedy sleeper.
好啦  好啦
All right. All right.
现在你得唱歌给我听
Yeah. And until then, you are going to sing to me.
因为收音机坏了  你又很自私  但歌声很好听
Because the radio's broken, and you are selfish, but you have a nice voice.
是喔  快唱
Really? Sing!
I wanna rock 'n' roll all night
真是开也开不完
Man, this is a long drive.
我的眼睛  睁开了吗
Are my eyes open?
没有
No!
早安
Morning. Aah!
嘿  老公
Hey. Hey, hubby. Heh.
我想找你讨论
Yeah. Actually, um, I wanted to talk to you...
注销婚姻的事
...about that whole annulment thing. Uh-huh?
我不打算去办
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
好
Okay. Heh.
那我们就维持婚姻关系
So we'll just stay married.
是的  没错
Yes, exactly.
我会请大家叫我盖勒太太
And I will make everyone call me Mrs. Geller.
真是太棒了
Wow, this is so amazing.
我还以为得加把劲说服你
I, uh, really thought I'd have to talk you into this more.
我现在怕了  因为你好像不是在说笑
Okay, see now I’m scared because I don't actually think you're kidding.
我不是啊
I'm not kidding.
听着  我
Look, I... I... Heh.
我不能有三次失败的婚姻
I can't have three failed marriages.
我不能  好吗
I can't, okay?
我不要当那个人
I am not gonna be that guy.
所以  我们要永远这样下去
So, what, we just stay married forever?
好  这
Okay, how...?
说真的  你有什么影响
How is this going to affect you, really?
我是说  偶尔填表格要打勾时
I mean, you fill some form out once in a while...
你就勾〝已婚〞那一格
...instead of checking the box "Miss," you check the box that says, "Mrs."
就在〝未婚〞旁边
It's right next to it.
好  抱歉  你说得对  我们确实
Ohh, Okay. I'm sorry, you're right. You know what?
可以维持现状
We absolutely can stay married, ...
我还以为那两格离得很远
...because I was under the impression that the boxes boxes were far away from each other.
好  你就
All right. Look, just...
请你冷静下来
...please take a moment here...
想一想  你在叫我做什么
...and think about what you're asking of me. Okay?
我在请你帮我一个忙
I am asking you to do me a favor.
你是要我当你的老婆
You are asking me to be your wife.
而身为我的老婆  你应该帮我这个忙
And, as my wife, I think you should grant me this favor.
那个小孩踢得好用力
That kid kicked me really hard.
是你扯他的头发
Well, you did pull his hair.
他拿我的零食  我不想再争了
He took my snack. I'm not getting into this again.
好啦  说真的  真的很痛
All right, you know what? Hurts really bad.
我就叫你不要走路  来
Well, I told you not to walk. Here.
来吧
There. There. Okay.
这没有任何含意吧  没有
This doesn't mean anything, does it? No.
好
Okey.
你怎么可以让人搭便车
How could you pick up a hitchhiker?
他搞不好是强  强暴犯或杀人犯什么的
He could be a rape... He could be a rapist or a killer or something.
你以为我没有先问过吗
Don't you think I asked him that before he got in?
我不理你了  你睡你的觉
Y’know what? I'm not talking to you. You go back to sleep.
你  你是强暴犯吗  不是
And, you, are you a rapist? No.
你喜欢车上游戏吗
Do you like car games?
喜欢  你会牌照游戏吗
Yeah, you know the, uh, license plate game?
我最喜欢牌照游戏了
I love the license plate game!
我也要玩  我也要玩
Ooh, I'll play. I'll play.
不行  你需要睡眠  晚安
No, you need your sleep. Night-night. Shh.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
听着  我知道你想找我谈
Listen. I know you wanted to talk to me...
但我有个办法  或许能让你愿意维持现状
...but I have an idea that may make you wanna stay married.
我们登记注册  礼物都给你
We register and you get to keep all the presents.
不行  罗斯  你听我说
No, Ross, come on. No, listen.
我一直在想要怎么表达
look I've thought about how to tell you this, and, um,
罗斯  总之我们不能维持婚姻关系
the bottom line, Ross...is we cannot stay married.
那可不一定  当然一定
I don't know if that's true... Oh, but it is.
你知道吗
Ahem. Okay. You know what this is?
这就叫做意见不合
This is a difference of opinion.
在婚姻中遇到这种状况  罗斯
When that happens in a marriage... Oh, Ross, come on!
这不是  这不是婚姻  这是全世界最惨的宿醉
This is not, this is not a marriage! This is the world's worst hangover!
罗斯  听着  如果你不去注销   我也会去
Ross, listen, if you do not get this annulment, I will.
好  我去就是了
All right. All right, I'll do it.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿  嘿
Hey, hey, um...
对了  有没有注销婚姻送礼会
...uh, is there any such thing as an annulment shower?
等等  火车站在那里  我该下车了
Wait! Wait! There's the train station, where I get off.
我有你的住址和电话号码
Well, I have your address and phone number.
我知道你的名字和你居无定所
And I have your name and the fact that you're a drifter.
那主动权在你手上
So ball's pretty much in your court.
好  再见了
All right. See you, Pheebs.
拜托啦  菲比  我受不了了
Come on, Pheebs, I can't take this anymore.
求求你跟我说话
Please talk to me.
让我补偿你
Let me make it up to you, huh?
Ground control to Major Tom
Commencing countdown Engines on
Take your protein pills And put your helmet on
Pssh, this is...
闭嘴  够了
Stop it! Stop it! No.
不公平   你明知我无法抗拒  你那美妙的歌声
That's not fair. You know I can't resist that beautiful voice.
菲比  我真的很抱歉
Pheebs, look, I am so sorry.
我答应让你旅途愉快
I know I promised you a fun road trip with your friend...
却没做到
...and I didn't deliver, okay?
现在我知道  你认为保持清醒  对友情很重要
But-but-but now I know that you think being awake is an important part of friendship.
以后我会永远努力保持清醒
So I will strive to stay awake for as long as I know you.
你晚上还是可以睡觉什么的
You can still sleep at night and stuff.
谢谢
Thank you.
那可以玩20个问题了吗
So can we play 20 Questions now?
我在堪萨斯就想到了一题  很棒的
I got a good one. I thought about it since Kansas.
好吧
Okay.
是一种
Is it...
热食三明治吗
...a kind of hot sandwich?
对
Yes.
是肉丸潜水艇吗
Is it a meatball sub?
真不可思议
That is incredible!
你是大师
You are the master!
有虫
Aah! Bug!
真好玩  你看起来就像要  别说了
Ah! That's funny. You look like you're... Don't say it!
想都别想
Don't even think it.
不说就不说
All right.
钱德  你跟她耗吧
Okay Chandler, enjoy your handful.
我们要不要干脆结婚算了
All right, should we just, should we just get married?
就这么做  反正所有的征兆都叫我们结
Y’know? I mean should we just do it? All the signs are telling us to do it.
我不想理会什么征兆了
I'm sick of the signs.
这样太快了  我很满意现状  我也是
It’s too fast, I'm happy the way things are. Me too.
我不想改变  你想吗  不想
I don't want things to change! do you? No.
好  那就不要改变  一切维持现状
All right then, then nothing changes! Everything is great!  Everything stays the same!
你快去整理行李  已经三天了  我快捉狂了
And you go unpack because it’s been three days and it’s driving me insane!
别激动  又不是要结
Jeez, relax, it's not like we're mar... Aah, agh.
我在想啊  要是我
You know, I was thinking, what if I, uh...
在这里整理呢
...unpack here?
那你的东西都会在这里
All your stuff would be here.
那
Well...
要是我的东西都在这里呢
What if all my stuff was here?
那你就得跑来跑去
Then you'd be going back and forth all the time.
没道理嘛
it doesn’t make any sense.
那么
Okay.
要是我们同居呢  你懂我的意思吧
What if we live together, and you understand what I'm saying?
同居
Live together?
还是没有任何征兆
There've been no signs for that.
我问你  就是个征兆
Me asking is kind of a sign.
好  好
Yes! Yes! Yes! Okay!
好啊
Yes.
好  好  你等等
Okay. Okay, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
好  这是给你的钥匙  给你钥匙
Okay. Here's your key. Here's your key.
你得出去  算正式启用
Now go out and christen it!
出去再进来
Go out and come back in!
这扇门五年没锁了  不过也行
Door hasn't been locked in five years, but okay.
准备好了吗  好了
Ready? Ready!
有点问题  钥匙断了  我也进不去了
Okay, a little problem. The key broke in the lock and I can’t get in!
等等  天啊  我也出不去了
Wait. Oh, my God, I can't get out!
这不是征兆吧  不是  是钥匙很旧了
This isn't a sign! No, it’s not a sign! it's a very old key!
钥匙太旧了  旧得不得了
It's an old key! Oh, my God, it's old.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
你有抱着门吗
Are you hugging the door right now?
没有
No.
好  我也没有
Yeah, yeah, me neither.
嘿
Hey.
手续办得还顺利吗
So did everything go all right with the annulment?
没问题   都办好了
Oh, yeah. No problems. It's all taken care of.
罗斯  谢谢你
Ross, thank you.
你们要不要去看电影  好啊
Hey, do you guys wanna go see a movie?  Oh yeah, why not?
菲比
Pheebs?
不了  眼前就有一出
No thanks, I've already seen one.
嘿  我去穿毛衣  好
Okay, um, I'm gonna get my sweater. Okay.
想不想听一件奇怪的事
Okay. You uh, you wanna wanna hear something weird?
当然
Always.
我没去办注销
I didn't get the annulment.
什么  我们还是夫妻
What? We're still married.
不要告诉瑞秋   待会儿见
Don't tell Rachel. See you later.
（献给真的结婚的寇妮与大卫）
你在干什么
What are you doing?
钥匙断在钥匙孔里了
Key is stuck in the lock.
我会修  等下
I can fix it. Hold on.
让开  让开
Watch out, watch out.
还是打不开
It still doesn't work.
我还没弄完  噢
I'm not finished. Oh.
漂亮   你的技术真好
Nice job, Joe. You are quite the craftsman.